solidcommerce.com 2017-08-29

# Privacy Policy | Solid Commerce

### Call **us** at (800) 750-7617

Welcome to Liquidate Direct LLC dba Solid Commerce (“Solid Commerce”). We understand that your privacy online important to you, especially when conducting your business. This Privacy Policy describes the Solid Commerce practices for gathering, storing, using and disseminating information. By visiting this website you agree to be bound by the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree with the terms and conditions set forth below, please do not use or access the Solid Commerce services. By accepting this Privacy Policy, you expressly consent to the use and disclosure of your personally identifiable information as outlined below. This policy may be changed from time to time. All changes will be posted to this site and you are encouraged to periodically check back to this site for any changes to the privacy policy.

Solid Commerce provides technology and services that enables online retailers (“Solid Commerce Client(s)”) expand their sales and marketing efforts across multiple online channels to acquire customers (“Buyers”) and maximize inventory yield. Solid Commerce is committed to maintaining the privacy of its users, including both Solid Commerce Clients and Buyers. If you have accessed this Privacy Policy by clicking on the privacy policy link on a site other than the Solid Commerce web site, your information may be collected by Solid Commerce as a service to the entity that controls such other web site and the Solid Commerce privacy policy terms will apply to the collection of your personal information.

#### INFORMATION COLLECTION

If you are using the online marketplace services of Solid Commerce (the “ **Services** “), whether through the Solid Commerce website or a Solid Commerce Client site powered by Solid Commerce, Solid Commerce may collect personal information about you including billing and shipping addresses, credit card purchasing information, product information and product order information. In addition, Solid Commerce may also collect information about your bidding, buying and selling history as well as third party comments regarding your bidding, buying and selling behavior. Bidding and buying history may specifically include your history with respect to any failure to complete sales on winning bids. Solid Commerce will collect any comments you may send to Solid Commerce and any information you may post to the Solid Commerce site or a Solid Commerce Client site powered by Solid Commerce. Solid Commerce may also collect information through the use of Cookies (as defined below).

Solid Commerce collects personal information when you: (1) register with Solid Commerce, (2) become a Solid Commerce Client, (3) participate in an auction for a product listed by a Solid Commerce Client, (4) complete a checkout page for a product purchased from a Solid Commerce Client, (5) provide comments or submit a problem to Solid Commerce or a Solid Commerce Client, (6) request information from Solid Commerce and provide your name or return contact information, or (7) respond to special offers, contests or surveys. As part of the registration or checkout process, you may be asked to provide contact and billing information and other personally identifying information. Providing some of the requested information is optional and Solid Commerce will indicate what information is required and what information is optional.

#### USE AND DISCLOSURE OF PERSONALLY IDENTIFYING INFORMATION

Bidding and Buying Process. If you are a Buyer and you are involved in a transaction with a Solid Commerce Client (for example, a seller of an item you are purchasing), we share personally identifiable information about you with that Solid Commerce Client in order to assist you with the bidding and buying process as well as to assist Solid Commerce Clients with the selling process. Solid Commerce will retain your information at Solid Commerce to support the transaction. To the extent that Solid Commerce Clients have access to your personally identifiable information, these entities will treat this information in no less a secure manner than they treat the personally identifiable information of customers who purchase directly through the web site of that Solid Commerce Client. If you are a Buyer, you are encouraged to review the privacy policies of the Solid Commerce Clients that provide the products or services related to your bid or purchase. You should contact Solid Commerce Clients directly and review their privacy policies should you have questions concerning their use of your information such as, for example, communications you may or may not wish to receive.

Client Support. Contact information provided by you in connection with problems, comments or requests is used only to respond to those problems, comments or requests and may be provided to Solid Commerce Clients or third parties as necessary to respond to the comment, problem or request.

Marketing/Special offers/Solicitation from Solid Commerce. Solid Commerce may use registration information to provide updates, and other business purposes related to making available the features and functions of Services. Solid Commerce also may use registration information and checkout information to make you aware of new products or special offers or promotions. Solid Commerce will abide by requests from you (in accordance with the section below) to discontinue such use. If you are a Buyer: you will not receive such information as described in this section. As a Buyer, if you receive communications directly from a Solid Commerce Client, you should contact the Solid Commerce Client directly concerning such communications and review their privacy policies.

Providing Your Information to Third Parties for Marketing/Solicitation.

If you are a Solid Commerce Client, Solid Commerce may provide certain of your registration information to third parties for use in marketing and in designing or providing their own services, to send you information about its products and to notify you if you win a contest. You may opt-out of Solid Commerce providing such information to third parties at any time by updating your Personal Account Settings or by contacting Solid Commerce, as set forth below. You should contact the third party directly who may already be sending you messages in order to request these communications stop, and to review their privacy policies.

If you are a Buyer, (1) Solid Commerce does not sell your information to third parties for purposes of marketing or soliciting you, provided however, we may share personally identifiable information, including credit or debit account information, with a third party upon your prior consent; and (2) To the extent that Solid Commerce Clients (for example, a seller of an item you purchased) have access to your personally identifiable information as a result of your bidding or buying (reference C (1) above, where Solid Commerce provides your information to Solid Commerce Clients as part of a transaction you may be involved in with such Solid Commerce Client), these entities may solicit or market to you in accordance with their policies. As a Buyer, you are encouraged to review the privacy policies of the Solid Commerce Clients that provide the products or services related to your bid or purchase. You should contact Solid Commerce Clients directly and review their privacy policies should you have questions concerning their use of your information such as, for example, communications you may or may not wish to receive.

Bidding, Buying, Selling History. Solid Commerce may use any information collected related to your bidding, buying or selling history to generate recommendations and predictions related to likelihood of your willingness to complete a bid and may submit such history and recommendations to Solid Commerce Clients.

Other Disclosures. Solid Commerce may disclose your personal information if required to do so by law or if Solid Commerce has a good faith belief that such disclosure is necessary to protect and/or defend the rights and interests of Solid Commerce. Solid Commerce may, as permitted by applicable law, disclose your personally identifiable information to Solid Commerce Clients, other Solid Commerce users or third parties in connection with an investigation of fraud, infringement, piracy or other unlawful activity and you expressly authorize Solid Commerce to make such disclosures.

Domestic and International Use. All personally identifying information collected by Solid Commerce may be used in the United States or if the Services are undertaken by Solid Commerce for a foreign Solid Commerce Client, such information may be transferred to that Solid Commerce Client outside of the United States and you consent to any such transfer of information outside of your country.

#### REVIEW AND MODIFICATIONS TO YOUR PERSONALLY IDENTIFYING INFORMATION

If you are a Solid Commerce Client, you may add, modify or update your personal information by accessing your account settings from the Solid Commerce home page when you log in to the Services. Through your Personal Account Settings, you may also determine how and when that personal information is distributed.

If you are a Buyer Solid Commerce may retain transactional history in order to document a transaction you may have had with a Solid Commerce Client. You should contact the Solid Commerce Client (for example, the seller of an item you have purchased) directly in order to access, modify or update your personal information with them.

#### LINKS TO OTHER SITES

As a part of the Services, Solid Commerce provides links to web sites operated by third parties, including entities with whom Solid Commerce has engaged in special relationship (“Partners”). Solid Commerce is not responsible for the information collection or privacy practices or the content of third party sites or of its Partners. You are encouraged that you read the privacy policy on the website of such third parties and Partners.

#### SECURITY

Solid Commerce stores personally identifiable information obtained through registration securely and considers it part of the assets of its business. To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the appropriate use of information, Solid Commerce has put in place physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information it collects online. However, data security is a constantly evolving art and science. You should consider any communication that you transmit to Solid Commerce (such as data, questions or answers, comments, or suggestions) as non-confidential, and agree that Solid Commerce will not be liable or responsible if information that belongs to you is intercepted and used by an unintended recipient.

#### COOKIES

“Cookies” are data files that may be downloaded to your computer when you visit the Solid Commerce site or a Solid Commerce Client site powered by Solid Commerce and permit the Solid Commerce server to identify your browser whenever you interact with the Solid Commerce site or a Solid Commerce Client site powered by Solid Commerce. Solid Commerce uses cookies to recognize repeat visits by users of its site and to collect information about its users’ interactions with the Services. These cookies contain identification information that enables us to streamline your experiences using the Services. You may set your browser software to reject cookies, but you will be required to reenter your login information each time you access the Services, and you may not be able to optimize the features of the Services. In some cases, you will not be able to access Services if cookies are disabled.

#### CHILDREN

Solid Commerce uses reasonable efforts not to collect, use or disclose individually identifiable information from children under the age of 18. The Services are not targeted at children, and children may not register for any of the Services. Solid Commerce Clients are required to be a business capable of entering into a legally binding contract.

#### FURTHER INFORMATION

If you have any questions about anything in this Privacy Policy or about collection of personally identifiable information, or information generally, please contact Solid Commerce as follows:

Liquidate Direct, LLC DBA Solid Commerce

Attn: General Counsel  
12021 Wilshire Blvd., Suite 530  
Los Angeles, CA 90025

Tel: 800-750-7617  
Fax: 310.388.0765  
Email: privacy@solidcommerce.com

You may also use the above contact information if you think any information about you is inaccurate, incomplete, or if you want to change the sort of information about you that Solid Commerce may have collected. Solid Commerce reserves the right to modify or amend this Privacy Policy at any time to the extent permitted under applicable law. Your continued use of the Solid Commerce website and Services following the posting of changes will mean that you accept those changes.

If Solid Commerce is merged, sold, acquired or transfers all or substantially all of its assets to another entity, Solid Commerce reserves the right to transfer personally identifiable information to any such third party who many acquire all or substantially all of the assets of Solid Commerce by merger, sale, or transfer of any of its divisions or business units.
